Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
We are Kangol
Hey what's up guys? How are you?
Hi Dave. I don't know this thing pops off my
light thing. Hold on. There we go. Okay. Good enough.
What's up guys, hi, you're being harassed on Benny's live.
Oh, I'm sorry Cheyenne, hey, what's up, nice to meet you.
Hold on, what do I want?
Oh, hold on, who's, oh, no, no, oh, Jamie's good.
Jamie's a friend, okay, so yeah, Cheyenne,
I just met Cheyenne on Benny's live.
Guys, I was just on Benny's show, you know, Benny Blocko.
If you don't know Benny Blocko, he's like, basically,
Told him he like gave birth to me unto the panel versus there's like one person that was like well
I want to do kind of what he's doing, you know in a similar way, you know my own way, but I
Someone that was really hey spunky. How are you? Yeah? Oh
Hi, yeah, I saw you I saw your memories. I am you're welcome here
Yeah, so I was on his show and I just thanked him and he's like he's here
I think he said oh, we were just they were just talking about me or something because they were
Talking about how he's like whoa. He's like well
He's like awake and used to come in here and I got you know, do Terry's asked me help me get subscribers
And I helped him do the first 50 and he's like
And then we talked about some cool stuff like you know music is Marty be on the show
Thank you afraid of Benny. He called you a bit. Oh
Don't well if you did that. I don't know. What did you say to him? I don't know
And I'm gonna make sure you're an adult, right?
You're um, you're to me in the chat you have to be over 18. Okay?
Just let me know
Okay
Hi guys, how are you doing tonight? Wow, July 5th?
Yeah, I am
Had a nice shower
You told him to drink water. Oh, well, yeah, sometimes see
And as you overreact right
But yeah, you know what guys, you know, what's funny too is like now. I'm like I was always screaming
Oh, you know who you turn, you know, Emma and who turned, uh, you know, Benny against me
I was like blade this guy played and then everyone's like, no
You know, they said they never never leave me and I but I knew I saw this guy doing the stuff
And finally, because I wasn't finding his mods,
so I would see what would go on.
And I knew that a lot of his donors and stuff
were being hidden or kind of scared away or something.
And it turns out that it was Blade.
And he figured out it was Blade.
Yep, if I buy, I did a woman once,
but I don't think I'd get one again, not nothing.
just it was my thing but I don't know but anything's possible
uh he called you basically that's important yeah well he had some Justin just a homeboy
hey Cheyenne hey five
donkey jayme charisma hi
it's Patrick and I saw tarot tarot does where's the Hebrew hammer he's in here somewhere
You remember came thanks guys for stopping by Samantha Avery of course first one in the chat
Like usual, okay?
Yeah
You didn't hear what I said on just now or in the on the panel. Can you please see your key?
Yeah, you can it's tricks right here. Here's tricks. I have a few in the I have a few in the house here
Well, this is this is not the one I showed on Benny's. This is the tricks. I showed Lola on Benny's but that's tricks
Did I wake you up? Oh, I just woke you up. Can I give you scratches on your neck?
Oh, little scratches. I give you some little scratches. Oh
Tristan, yeah, let's see. Of course. You want a new panel? Okay, come on.
But you're 21 over for the panel, please. Okay. If you're not, then you'll have to wait till you're 21.
Hi
Oh, that's Lenore here too. Lenore, do you want to say hi to you? Oh, oh, oh, wait, do you want me to pick up right now?
Oh, so this is Tricks. This is Mr. Tricks. This is Tricks. He's about a little over a year old.
Sweetheart.
Guys, I have a new deck, the new deck is here.
It's just, I have to go down the stairs, grab it,
so I'll do some reads from that tonight.
It's easy, coms, oh, well, I don't know,
easy if I'd be mad at me, I do put it back.
Sometimes I put people backstage, sometimes I just, like.
Like I just need silence, you know, and instead of just muting I just look clear at the stage so I can go
Oh, you're not joining. Oh, no, no, you don't have to join panel. No, but thank you. Nice to nice to meet you
hope you're doing okay and
You know Benny Benny come kind of you be right back. You want to check out Benny? Go check out Benny
Okay, tell everyone hi. It was fun fun being in that chat
Then he's a cool cool guy, but he was very cool. He seems like a little bit, you know, he's
Chris was oh Chris K was there too. And so I was like, hey, just any three things like they're trying to figure out
Like, well, how do you make money? And then someone said only fans. Oh, here we go. Oh my gosh, Trevor
There
How we doing friends?
How are you good, sir?
Yeah, did you see me or no you missed it?
I was just on what's that? Oh
You know what I did tune in for just a second
Oh, yeah, I did how was that?
How's that go? It's so good
Was it many Benny and I are very nice. What do you guys talk about?
No, I'm just kidding. Are you really sweet? No, it was it was Chris. It was Chris K. You know Chris K who Chris K is
Oh, yeah, I've seen kid. Can I tell you a story about Chris K? The first time I ever saw him
was he came on panel. It was a stream called
The the kid I say kid, but I think he's in his 30s like me PJ. He went by he did
Real streams is what he called it was like a drama network
all of a sudden this guy comes on and I'm like holy shit is that the guy from
anthrax is that the lead singer from anthrax and it was Chris K he looks like
he looks exactly like the guy from anthrax he has the beard in the whole
thing I don't think you would have said Fred Durst or something Fred Durst or
Yeah, no, do you know who I'm talking to the guy for?
Scott Scott Scott Scott something I don't know
I think Ian something. I don't know
What's been so long?
I was on Benny's panel earlier, I was reading him the riot act about of course he was going
on earlier about how he was going to punch his mom in the face and threaten her this,
that, and the third and you know I was trying to say hey, hey cool down little fella.
Cool down, but he didn't want to hear that of course you didn't want to hear that you're in a good mood
I'm glad I caught him the last couple times in good moods, but and I told him I invited him to my show
He's like oh, he's like when are you on I'm like I'm on every guys that I just did a 19 hour stream like today
So so I'm on a lot
Yeah, I started league again that like very uh, like like late last night
I slept all day yesterday, and I woke up at like five six or seven started streaming and I streamed until like
Two in the afternoon or three in the afternoon. I took maybe four in four
That's okay. It was just it was like it was 18 hours by that
And I don't know if my stream will ever be available because it's so over like the 12 hour limit
So it's not ready yet. The video is not ready
That's the longest was that the one yeah, cuz I really love I usually cut it up at 12 hours
But this but then no sometimes I fall asleep, and then it will run and it will just automatically cut out when everyone leaves, but
That was an active panel
nice nice I used to do streams myself many years ago many years ago and I'll
be god damned if I couldn't make it to the one-hour mark like 40 minutes in I'm
like okay this is enough
Goodbye
I would do one hour a week when I first started every like I'd be thinking all we got what do I do like well
What am I gonna do this like this week? I think of the further one hour
And I was like then I would like I but I was able to like that that I wasn't doing the streaming area
I was just doing the lives was just me talking and so it did feel like a lot and it's like kind of it's hard
Just talking to the chat. I got my little cell phone doing it. I
Don't know how I started out. So with all everything's like so difficult, but now it's like
I'm really going good. It's going good. Good. You're a star.
We're three diamonds here. Like three diamonds and some obscene things on my show when she
was on last night and she kept then she porn bought me and then I then I deleted the episode
but I guess I deleted the wrong one. Yeah. It's like the transgender. Is that the is
Well, there you go. Okay. Fair enough. I love everyone. I love everyone.
Yeah, it is. No, we love you too. It's like, I was always so nice, but then she was like,
on shows, like, oh, Psyche's called me. She said, he said, I look like a man. She's like that.
Psyche's Oscar the Grouch. He's like, in a dirty house, and he's like, he's a gross,
and he just likes fish taco and dick. She called you Oscar the Grouch.
Is that what she said? Yeah, she said, Oscar the Grouch.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, but tell me how old you are just tell me how old you are so I just know you're okay to be in this chat because it's an adult
Chat, please doesn't yeah
Did you say 21 and older is that what we're keeping in that?
On the panel and then the chat I'm participating 18 or older you're right here. Just sure I know
But I'm like I was really like your Chris K is like yeah, you're 18. Okay, so you're okay, so
Guys 18 so I'm not okay. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
That he that's the first thing. I thought he looks like the the anthrax lead singer
Have you ever listened to a little anthrax
Uh, yeah, I mean one of those CDs I got like, you know, one of those like BMG or Columbia house
You know, you said these CD clubs
That um, they send you like eight CDs or ten CDs or whatever for like honey a CD and I would get an anthrax CD
I think I was too young to appreciate the time. I was probably a six or seventh grade
I would get these big boxes of CDs and then
And then they started sending like individual CDs and charging like $30 per CD
No, I'm not mad. I'm not mad, but I just, I'm not sure. It's just, uh,
don't worry about Benny. I just can't hang on the chat. Okay.
So
Yeah, yes, indeed. Yeah, yes indeed. I
What is God is what's that a magical feeling? Oh my god?
It was a Christmas Christmas morning when you get all those CDs. Okay, you got all these CDs in a box
And then it's like if you don't even cost anything
It's like well, then they said you're like a little bill for like five dollars
But then they start jacking up the price and they said you're like, oh, here's your CD of the month
and it's like some CD you don't even want and it's like 27 dollars for one CD like what the hell
but i was i was a minor so my dad would write to them and say oh you can't make a contract with a minor
and then they would oh so was i i did that same exact shit i did that say because they wouldn't
even ask for a credit card they would not ask for a credit card they'd be like what's your income
this that and uh and the other and you you would just make it up and
Like two weeks later, you would have like a frickin package like ten CDs
It was it was the greatest thing ever. It was the greatest thing ever my god
Hey Trevor, you have a you have a question in the chat so much Cheyenne asked
Seiki what does Trevor do like hobbies? So what do you do for your hobbies Trevor? That's a good question
I come on panel when I talk to you, sir.
Okay.
I come on panel when I talk to you.
I think his hobby is like twinks and panels.
I'm not sure.
Is there anything else that should add to the list?
Twinks and panels?
There you go.
Basically, my day consists of listening to music, podcasts, listening to different streams,
and I do a little freelance work, a little freelance work online to pay for my alcohol
addiction, to pay for my beers, if you will, but yeah, that's about it for me, nothing
too interesting.
Nothing too interesting.
This is the highlight of my day right here.
Hell yeah.
This is the highlight.
Not a lot of people know about open panels on YouTube.
Like I mean, because comparatively,
it's a very kind of a smaller,
it's a very niche kind of area of YouTube,
but not a lot of people are aware of how cool it is
to have like these fun chat rooms.
I don't know, you have to kind of,
you have to kind of fall across one by accident, I think.
And it's like, so it's like,
kind of like I pull you into a different universe, right?
It's been quite a journey, but I
Think I mean, I mean the way out of the rabbit hole for the most part, but you know, I'm not gonna forget what I saw down there
Hey for the sake of conversation, can I
Can I can I speak on something you were saying earlier?
Yes
Bro, and I'm not I'm not an insider of who was Benny's mods or whatever. I'm just a I'm just a
36 year old gay pervert who's been watching Benny since he started streaming literally day one a few years ago
And I know how Benny is he gets drunk he blocks people
It wasn't blade. It wasn't blade. It was Benny. He gets drunk as fuck
He blocks people and then he can't remember and then he gets paranoid
Okay, but he'd be with girl. Yeah, play with the block and anyone
Well, maybe play what I don't know 100% sure because I wasn't a mod anymore
And I never saw blade really do anything, but he's a pervert. He's a he's a friendly pervert. He's not really a
He's not a bad pervert. Okay. Yeah, he likes he likes
Vinny Blanco type twinks, okay.
You're confused.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Maybe the show might be too much for you.
Okay.
I keep it up on bar folks, I keep it up on bar.
It's all, it's all, it's all jokes, okay?
So what was the question Trevor?
I'm sorry, I'm a little bit, I'm pretty good.
Ben Benny well because of the the whole thing with the girls and that's that and yeah, okay. Well, so yeah, so
late late wasn't my discord and
Would when females would come into my discord
He would okay first of all
He would like chase away any guy that came in the discord and then the females who have getting their inbox right away and start like
They would start sending new Sam. He posted revenge for post revenge pictures of piranha on my
My discord is what happened
He she had said I'm sorry. Oh, that's the other message of the north to jump it over there. Yeah, she's not she's not something down
But yeah, she's like
Few few like, you know personal photos like erotic photos been he posted on the discord
I kicked him off the discord. He just like he went crazy on me
He like Emma turned against me some people are saying Janet's it did it some people are saying it was it was
No, both of them both of them saying that they said the same thing to Emma
So Emma's getting two people coming saying talking shit about me, but it's most of my friends at the time, right?
Who knew I like really liked her? I think at least I must have seen the same things
But just ignored it, you know or didn't really care, but Emma Emma chicken look like I'm sinker. Do you want?
I never had a problem with light. I never had a I mean we worked
I'm not on the freaking Benny board or Benny Brad discord or anything. I never
I'd never had an issue with him and by the way, why would he I
Hate when people pick such a like blade like there's
But I never had an issue with him. Well, he wasn't he wasn't Ip2. He was just some basically just a mod for Benny
but
He yeah, he was a mod for Benny
I introduced him to at least in everything he became a mod for for Emma
You know, he started this infiltrating his way into shows and he's so innocent, but he's okay, but the thing is he's like
If we started talking about Benny, he would start to cry on the phone.
He grew his hair exactly like Benny, wore it the same way.
He did the little like the bangs and he would do the little same face in his photo.
And then he, he ordered the same, the lady of the castle art print for his wall.
And he was like, oh, Benny invited me to come see him.
It was like single single wife female single. Are you saying? Yeah, it's true. I mean, I don't lie
That's why I remember all the details because they're obviously true
My real name that's that's uh
That is confidential
He says I don't always hang out with the most masculine gay guys, so I felt complimented
He said he could never say a crossword to any of my gay friends because
They're so built LMAO. Yep. Have you met spunky? Hold on
It's Trevor, I'm spunky
Spunky nice to meet you. How are you? I'm free babe. How are you?
You're out and about it looks like you're out and about what I'm the town. I'm hiding in the parking lot
Justin is over there at the bar
Got her boyfriend in the bar
Oh, hi. What's all your bar? Nice. Thank you. I just pulled a trick on him because I'm drunk
What'd you do?
Okay, so Justin constantly thinks
I'm not very cute. Wish I don't lie
And we were at the bar and there was this cute,
like 23 year old guy across the bar, like eyeing me up.
And Justin's like, why is that guy staring at us?
And I'm like, cause he's checking me out.
And he's like, no, no, he's not.
And I'm like, no, I'm at the age where 23 year olds
like check mills out and that's what happens.
Like that's what they do.
He's trying to see if I'm with you or not.
So I said, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to go say, how did that guy on the way back?
and I'll have him give you a thumbs up if you're checking me out, so I went over to the guy
across the bar and I was like, hey, so I was sitting at the bar with my verse on over there
and he doesn't believe that you were checking me out. Were you checking me out? If you were,
can you give him a thumbs up? And this guy like turned around and he was like...
Yeah, it was hilarious. It was great. That's so funny. It was really cute. Yeah, and then he was pissed. Oh, he was mad
No
Was a guy is a guy and a bloody poop on the floor
Do you want to see him? I'll put him I'm gonna mute it and I'll go show you. Oh, oh this guy says hang on this
This guy says he's super handsome
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
Chaka Chaka
Um, I was like I was at the Mattel like the Mattel headquarters and she was like in a glass case as a prototype for
One of the Barbie night freed me. Yeah
Free me from it's held. Oh
Yeah, oh my god
Show us your coffee can on his stream it would mess it up, but I know
Do you guys do you like transsexuals?
I know what I know a Mexican transgender woman
She has
Woman I am a Mexican
Okay, okay
Oh my god
Other self for them in transition to a man. Oh my god
Show us your chocolate nipples. Oh, yeah
Yeah
He's a real man, you're a real man, right? You're a man, right?
Don't tell you
Are they both are they both are they both wearing that shirt they're putting on each other. No, no, that's the shirt
Do that what's going on down there
Yeah
Oh, thank you a little streaming for you. Just one nipple. You got to buy nipples
Okay
What's your channel called? I did terrible things and like I get drunk in a party and like
Yeah, there are a bunch of cute cute girls
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's yeah, come on guys. We can do
Yeah
That was a good bump, what's your name Daniel? I have one name you have one name Daniel. What's your name? I'm Corbin
Corbin, that's my son's name.
Sorry, I just said that.
Wow, that's crazy.
Corbin, Corbin.
He's broke.
You know that song?
Daniel's been with a guy before, I can tell.
Yeah.
Daniel's been with a guy before.
Did your mom ever say that woman band?
Yes.
I don't know.
I think I was born before that.
Not sure when I moved.
You look a little bit older than him.
How old are you?
I'm 29.
Yeah, yeah.
You're older than that.
Oh, I'm not sure what my son is.
Stephanie.
That's the guy who's been with another guy, I can tell.
Oh.
But that game I definitely said I was at your middle name Michael. Yeah, his is not
Did you just hear that psyche they were coming in Anthony
Yeah, I've heard that song.
All right, go Pete.
I'm back.
Should I go with him to hold it?
Yeah, hold it for him.
Saki, do you want me to go in the bathroom with them so you can watch him hold it?
Yeah, sure.
I think it would be great for the stream.
Oh, wait, we can't put it on the stream, right?
Yeah.
No, we can see this.
I guess we can see the stream, but we can't see the...
We can see the stream, but we can't see the wiener.
Sorry.
Okay.
It's okay.
Take him back.
We'll be right back.
I'll say it later.
I can't see everything else tonight.
Wow
The gays love you though, you know, you got you got that
I'm family I'm safe yeah yeah good good good yeah and they can tell they can totally tell
look at Justin look at Justin at the bar what is he's like what the hell
what is he doing out there talking about these gay guys you're gonna go okay we're going
ahead like five gay guys who the fuck is talking to my woman
oh he doesn't care no he doesn't care I can tell you that
He does not care he's very secure. Well with that at least
Okay, did I finish my story about what are you doing? Yeah? Yeah, you didn't prank. Yeah, I was crazy
Yeah, they seem really nice and they're already my cock, you know, so wow
I'm blessing. Yeah, I think I think I've never talked to more guys
Yeah
Here we go
Oh, she's she's a wild card. Is she not? She's all about
Drunk and having fun
Getting drunk and having fun psych. Are you still there? Yes. I'm here. I just put her up. I'll put myself in there
Here we go. I'm no I did it. Oh my god. Oh, is that Justin? Yeah, there you are. Is that Justin the boyfriend or the husband?
He said I'm not allowed to oh, he said no. He said no filming
Um, yeah, that's not a rabbit. That's uh, that's a that's a spunky
Wow, um, yeah, are you okay saying
He's oh, he sounds like a rabbit. Oh, oh no, Trevor. Yeah, Trevor's Trevor's the Easter Bunny
He's one of the Easter Bunnies. There's like a hundred of them
Yeah, people call me rabbit, I'm not sure why
Are you here to be are you here to be a rabbit that perverted guy that like always like oh little Benny?
I'm gonna take that guy's an asshole. That's not me that guy's an ass
Fucking asshole that guy is but yeah, she's
Yeah
Okay, look
There he is Trevor. How about that one hit that?
I can't see you. I can't even see you shit. Okay. He's really good just from a kiss
Okay, I got closer get closer so I can see god damn it. It's okay
The Mexican guys are coming back
For diamond, there's got some Mexican guys in the bathroom right now. They're coming back to get terrorese. I think
Yay
Bathroom those two guys fucking in the bathroom. I want my friend is
Want me to bring sure I'm not gay, but my friend is yes, and they're both gay. Well, what's it? I don't know
I don't know. I'm not sure
Exactly a hundred percent with
Yeah, he's gonna do drugs on the screen like just don't like just don't like inject anything or something like that. Okay, just like, you know
We're sitting on a bum on the stream. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Just look just kind of like
Okay, we don't see anything. Oh, did you hear that?
Yeah, she is beautiful, isn't she hot
You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty cute. You're pretty
How was it? Oh my gosh, how did it go? How did the dick fucking go?
I don't remember because I was like eight years old.
I was kidding. It was a joke. It was a joke. You said, yeah, he's an 80-year-old woman, an 80-year-old woman.
Also, I am drunk.
Okay.
Yeah.
So it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, you should go on there.
You should go on there.
You'll find him on there and look for where there's spunky.
That's me.
Justin away.
Justin.
You know, I'm going to look at him right now.
Okay.
Join my channel, we love Mexican guys, it's on YouTube.
Yeah, this is fucking good time, man.
You're live on YouTube in front of 24 people right now.
Right now, streaming, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, 24 people.
21, yeah, 24 people, guys.
We are on IRL, it's funky.
in a mystery location
Look say hi. I am I'm looking for you out for you all times. Thank you. Thank you new subscribers
You're moving five minutes the first guy you talked to
Yeah, yeah, it's all kind of weird. Yeah, let me see it. He is
I think it's a sky for me. Oh, that's him
He's gonna join and go on panel right now that's him look look there's you there's us
He's in the chat right now
Don't get in trouble. Wow. Wow guys
that was intense he was pretty cute he said i was cute he's straight what's rabbit's channel
um trevor oh i don't know if he really has a channel he's never asked to um to put it in the
chat or anything um trevor if you're in the chat and you have a channel um type your channel name
If anyone knows his name is Trevor Ryan, I'm not sure if it's the exact name.
It's like he rabbit screamed at Benny on a stream that he's upset. Did someone
check on him?
Just now that happened, what's going on? I can't leave my stream. It's like
it's like bad luck to leave my stream unattended. I always have to have a watcher for it.
If you do a stream, I'll come by. Oh yeah, that's very nice Hannah.
Oh, yeah, Jeff. Yeah
Awesome you're meeting people in the chat guys
But if you're a mod you can post
Your link for your channel if you're not a mod
You can go ahead and like let
And you like your link posted go ahead and give the channel name in the in the in the chat
Maybe hopefully maybe we'll be able to post your channel in there
I'm gonna go get my new cards though. I have these new cards
I think they're outside it said so I'm right there
It's cold
I think they put him in the mailbox, so I have to get the keys one second
Oh
Uh
Okay guys
Whoo
Okay, you're doing fall. Yeah, that's a cat. I'm okay. Everything's okay. Shayam
Okay
Yeah, let's see
Everything's fine cold in California. It's yeah, it's a little bit chilly right now
The wind is kind of blowing through the windows. You see it's all blowing
Okay guys the game
So this is
Thank you easy easy. I'm sorry. I'm a jerk sometimes. Let's see. I love you
Here's what I got these are called the inner worlds
Oracle cards
So this will be our unboxing
Psychi rabbit yelled up any way earlier got riled up and called me a bit. I know
Uh
He's a troll that's what he that's what he does you have such people that
Aren't aware. Okay
So here I read the back. It says the Oracle of the inner worlds deck. It says this
Oracle deck is your
cartographer for your inner world's intricate and even shifting landscapes.
Each card is a portal into the diverse realms within the quiet depths, the sunlit peaks,
and the tangled thickets and the altered skies of your unique consciousness.
Through evocative imagery and insightful messages, this deck helps illuminate hidden feelings.
unconscious patterns, limiting beliefs, and untapped potential.
It is designed to be a compassionate guide for your inward journey, offering clarity
for navigating your emotional and spiritual life, fostering self-acceptance and empowering
you to connect more deeply with the wisdom residing within your private universe.
Okay?
No, it's okay. I'm not mad at you. I'm not mad at you
Thank you. You know, I mean, it's okay. Just like, you know, just let Benny
Okay
Hey, Jeff, are you do you got the
Day the free child is upgraded. Yeah, do you need any questions about stringer? I can help you because I've been through the
Sure. Oh, these cards smell good. They smell really good. They're really pretty. I mean the back is pretty
But I've seen the I've seen the fronts of these cards. I don't know how exactly how
Psyche's the light is bothering my epilep. Okay. I got you. Oh my god. Oh my god. That's it
I don't want to give you a look. There you go. Okay
It's okay. I'm gonna have to start doing an epilepsy epilepsy warning for my show. Oh shit. These cards are really cool. Okay
Hi, babe. Hi, babe. So guys, let me just do I'll do three cards for the chat
I think these cards are also selfie I think that the meaning is put on them
So I'll do three cards for the this is for everybody here. Okay
Everybody here. We got 12 people in their chat. Okay. Connect with me
Hopefully I think there's gonna be messages that will help everybody a universal message that will help everybody in this chat
They'll relate to everybody that will help somebody okay
And I'll do it. I'll do I'll do I'll do three. Okay. Oh
You had almost I'm so sorry, I would feel terrible if my light did that I'm sorry
Did you miss spunky? Yeah, she was just here. She's out. I think she's a probably headed home. She was leaving a bar. That's some
cute cute
You guys
Okay
So here's three cards. Here's a three cards for the chat. These are brand new cards. Thank you easy our first card for the chat
Okay, so this is the first card
This card is inner flair. Okay
So maybe or yeah, so maybe you've got this like style about you. You've got like this little
Cute way of accessorizing, you just know the exact little touches, the makeup and the hair, everything's like got a little, everything's kind of perfect, but it says, it says, so the inner flair, it says sudden release, intense energy, emotional eruption, potent feelings, clearing pressure, vital revelation, passion, anger, sorrow, and insight.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much. Oh, no problem, Leah. So, yes, it says, deep, um, deep fires erupt, um, demanding passage.
Stand witness to the force. Raw power reveals its truth in the flare.
Yeah, I love you too. So this is like, you know, she's also, you know, she's also very hot
You know, she's got these red boots and she's got that red lipstick that really great blush
You know, I don't know. She's just hot, but she's got an inner fire. It's kind of like
Reflected on the outside, but you can tell there's more
Simmering down there. Okay, so I think you know, I think you had the glow up recently and
Increase the fire. Okay. Wow. Next we have this floating bliss and so there's floating bliss. Okay. It looks like a nice little easy chair
you know in the house
Kind of being carried in balloons or something you're floating. It says serene bliss
gentle upliftment
Interpeace inner peace soft beauty contentment receiving grace appreciation harmony quiet joy
And so after that like hot fire car that is hot. There's a hot
and glow up, you know, heat up,
then there's like this floating bliss.
There's all of a sudden there's this like cool breeze
and feeling of flying and floating.
It says, adrift gently into the currents of inner peace.
Simple beauty cradles you in a state of quiet joy.
Hey Nancy, okay.
So I hope after this hot card,
She's gonna be taking a little little air hot air balloon or hot hot couch balloon, whatever it is the house seems to be flying like a balloon
Also from your couch. You can be in the sky. You can do some meditations. You can calm your mind and you can actually
Travel right just don't go too far everybody. Okay, and like what is this one? Okay interesting
Finally
I'll maybe do one more card after this because they're so cool. I'm just getting these this one is called shadow marked
There's this is a shadow marked, okay?
Interesting what does this one mean shadow marked it says
evidence of inner
of inner journeys, integrated experience,
resilience through the shadow, earned wisdom,
owning history, visible strength, integrated sorrow.
It says your markings tell the story of your journey
through depth, wear them as emblems
of the strength and wisdom found within the shadows.
Okay?
Trannin the DEMP
What are you saying sake you don't feel good because of all the lights you have a small seizure was
Absence with seizure. You're good. No. I'm sorry drop the link. Okay. Sure. Here you go
You took your meds good good. I hope you're feeling better Cheyenne. Okay. Hey Nancy
Well, I really like I really like these and I think it's like
You know, it's definitely maybe
Maybe you feel like you caught on fire. You got really really hot there
to take a little bit of like getting out of the sun,
getting into the little shade of the house,
floating through the sky, getting a little cold breeze,
putting out, you know, the more intense flames.
You come out of it, you know?
This, it's shadow marked.
It's like, you know, this guy has some scars
or some evidence that he's been through a fire,
but, you know, he wears this like a,
like a, you know, like a design, like, you know.
There's beauty in it, too. Okay. Okay. I'll put my epilepsy up next time. Okay. Hi
Yeah, those are they were so cool you like
Hi, what are you doing? We're driving home. You drive home
Cool, I got my I got a new deck that the easy sponsored for me. It's really cool. They're oracle cards
They're called inner worlds oracle cards. They're really really pretty
No, I expect a hell Billy
He said he might want to get them for me. Yeah, I look forward to those
These are really cool. They were just really still really quick if I could just do a quick one for you
You can just if you thought okay
Okay, I'll pull a card for each of you if it's okay
Okay, so
Okay, okay, so this must be for Justin. So Justin this one someone says inner
Collage, how do I do here?
Inner collage
Yeah, it's an inner collage that says inner complexity
Diverse aspects layered self acceptance of complexity non harmonious wholeness
Observation, unique tapestry, and juxtaposition, and it says your inner world is a masterpiece
of juxtaposition, behold the rich tapestry woven from diverse and contrasting threads.
Yep, because you see it's like all these different threads, very different, you know, they come
together and create like almost like a stained glass.
You've got intercalage, yep, but you're able to take all those maybe discordant elements
and turn it into something beautiful and wonderful.
And for Spunky, you got this one.
It's called solitary reverie.
Spunky, you're always eating these hermit cards.
Everything's always telling you-
Yeah, I'm getting these cards.
It's telling me to go in my fucking hole.
Yeah.
Well, this one says solitude, introspection, reverie,
quiet reflection, processing thoughts, feelings,
inner stillness, personal space, simple pleasures.
It says under your inner light,
solitude becomes a sanctuary.
Sit quietly, reflect gently,
Builds profound wisdom. Okay, and I really you know, that's and that's that's always good
It's always good to have your personal
But you know also, you know
The two of you together that can be that's kind of solitude to when you two are together
Okay, okay, well this makes this ain't no room for each of you together each of you alone and
And then if there's a third option with people with other people make those like the three three different
I think I need to go in my hole with other people
Well, let's build it. Let's build a bomb shelter. We can
Pull people I attract
Look, yeah. Oh my god, like I I attract such cool people. Oh my god. I know the best
Yeah, Justin Justin gets annoyed when we go out to bars because they always attract like the weirdest weirdos and they're my favorite
Yeah, right Justin always
The weirdest weirdos and they are they are amusing. Sorry. He said that shit on your channel though. Oh, no, it's okay
I don't I didn't yeah
Yeah, the other guy said something
Well, yeah, that was really weird
Oh, what's it? I don't want to repeat it. It was something about like, um, I said, I said, I said, have you ever have you ever the guy or someone said, are you gay?
And he's like, no, I said, I've given a guy a blow job before. And then you said, and then you said, well, how old are you to give a guy a blow job?
And he's like, I was like, eight, eight. Wow. Yeah. Yeah. So it was kind of, uh-oh.
Yeah, awkward. Okay, but they're still there. They were there. They were there. They were so funny
And he's probably in here right now. So sorry awkward eight-year-old blowjob guy like welcome to the chat
Yeah, I know he comes in. Yeah
Well, it's fun. Yeah, I thought I'd just go on you know tonight
I'll probably go to bed a little earlier tonight because I was on so long today
But I had a great time today and that's my goal because I have work in the morning
Yeah, you gotta get your time schedule back on that. Yeah, like instead of staying up like all night
Okay, oh my god, I got a good hit
Oh, cool. I have a little bit left over Wendy's you want to say hi to Spunky Lola Lola wants to come say hi to you
Oh, she she's the one I love the most she has that resting bitch face like my little santi calf has
Yeah, and two tricks is right here tricks is right here. Yeah, are you home? Are you at home or at Justin's house?
Okay, that was fast. Nice little yeah, bar. Yeah
We have by the beach. I don't oh
Yeah, we're we're beach boys or Chris. That's what Chris K would say Chris
You there for Chris?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, my
Harder than me hardest strawberry pineapple. Oh, look my nails are good. Look how good my nails are tonight
I really scrape them out and cut them and stuff. It's like, you know
They've been picking on you and like they probably pick on me too because like mine are so little that I get dirt in them too
Look at my little sunset reckless. I have my heart tattooed on my pinky. Oh my gosh
And it's like on the front of it
Yeah, like on the cute Wow
Yeah, that's you. Wow
Well, it's very unique
And then I have this one
This is like I am greater than my highs and lows
But it doesn't have to do with like Jesus tattoos. It has to do with my blood sugars. So I'm a type one diabetic, so
Well, Rusty says that you look like her cat Jojo, and then you see them.
Um, Beata says I have a cat face, and that's why she thinks I'm pretty.
And it's a reality Nancy saying, Sponky's cute.
Yes.
Oh, that's sweet, Beata.
Yeah, Beata said that she finds me attractive because I have a cat face,
which I probably do because like, I have little like cat cheeks,
and I have the cat eyes.
And they're like green
Please thank you. Oh, yeah, there's going to chat Cheyenne. She's a little bit eccentric
Yeah, but I met her in the other chat. I was in Benny's and you know
Justin Boyle better tap that
Yeah
He has a timer too. Yeah rest rusty
You know Rusty, you know Rusty, I know Rusty. Hi Rusty. Rusty is a good girl. Yes
She's
Yeah, she's a lot of really cool people on here. Yes
And it's like it's even people that are like, you know people might like oh my god that person is like
They I don't know. We're all we're all a little bit offbeat, but it's I think people get to know us to they'll like us
You know, you know, some people have some shit to say about me, too, and I'm like, I'm not that bad, you know
Yeah, I can't believe what things people say and especially a
My show it's like I'm trying to like I don't know why these guys do this
It's like maybe if they're not getting laid. This is why there's just so
Rude and like that's how they treat every woman. I don't know any woman that would like that. It's just like there's a lot of rude shit
We're a lot of rude dudes
Rude Jews. Yeah, and so well, I think it on a full house
Yes, whatever happened to the predictability
Yeah, it's just Joe and I used like we go on Joe and I start seeing marathon songs of like TV introduction theme songs
We know all them by heart. We're such easy. Hey. Oh
Oh, oh
My god, I'm so sorry. Oh gypsy. I'm so sorry
Gypsy, I just saw that too. I'm so sorry. Oh
and like, you know, Jack has
such a cool cat he
You know, he was on her streams. She's just even Jim Teresa's to traveling gypsies to her
I never see jackass, but I'm so sorry gypsy. Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah, I knew him
He he was a and he was a great towns boy
He was due to tarot and he would like to put him out and he picker if he picked little cards and he would
Yeah, we love him. I'm sorry, and it was so hard. It's the worst. It's always the sweetest souls that go first
So Justin will live forever
I will die young. Oh come on. You are a sweet soul. You're both sweet souls. You're both
the forever. Maybe I'll share some. I'll share some. I'll share some with you. I'll share
some of his with you and you'll be even, right? Yeah, I don't know. I love you. I don't know.
You don't know. Okay. Hey, I love you, sweetie. You have fun. I love you, honey. I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye
Yeah, this book is really they sweet
Banging time up Justin was like get in here get in here now
As in as a boxers on the bed already probably
Saki how often do you stream? I don't want to leave I stream every day. So you know what?
You got it. You got your introduction and
So if you gotta go you got it you got it, but I'll be back, you know almost every day
So I'm on back and say hi next time
There's I got the link pinned
Surely everyone's doing great. I
Love you, too. You have a good night. Okay
Whoo
Theresa are you there because I got I mean I have these new cards. I have I can pull their oracle card
So if you'd like an oracle card, I got one for you
Okay
There's they're very they're just like it's like a nice nice art and a piece of okay, let's see
Okay, come through for Teresa, please.
Okay, so Teresa, this one is okay, so this says inner duality. Okay, and another beautiful
artistic owl. It says, duality, light and shadow, integration, acceptance,
wholeness, conflicting aspects, authentic power, and self-awareness.
It says, true wholeness arises not from choosing sides, but from courageously embracing the
vibrant dance of opposites within.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for letting us know.
That the rainbow bridge
dream the rainbow bridge Teresa is like, you know all animals will
Our beloved pets will go there and when we go to heaven we'll go and all of our
Pets throughout life. They'll all come running up to me to say so happy
right
It's just in talking about something inappropriate
I think he said he's gonna be banging like the hammer on the wall and they're gonna be hanging a picture painting. Okay
Okay, yeah awesome Teresa awesome Teresa thank you hope that I think that's a
good message is like you know we got the we got dualities no conflict and it's
like no we always conflict in feelings but you know within us we are we're
And reconciling these
Thank you. You obviously didn't see what else he said. Well, what's going on guys?
I'll be right back. I'm sorry here. Just give me the 30 second. I'm gonna check real quick
Okay, so Cheyenne is
Justin talking about something inappropriate. Who's just on Justin? Who's Justin?
Guys, you know, no, no, no, yes. Oh, Justin is oh, yeah, you know spunkies, huh?
Or boyfriend. Yeah
Guess he's talking about something inappropriate. No, he's just, you know, hammering nails.
Psyche, obviously didn't see what else he said. He deleted it. Psyche, as it was inappropriate.
Psyche, I think it was AI. What are you talking about? I have no idea what you're talking about.
Are you okay? I don't want to like, or being a little bit, think a little too many things.
Cheyenne
Justin hey, what's up guys anyone who wants the card? I think I
Want to pull some cards for the chat or anybody these are just
Do I do readings? Yes, I do do readings. I'm just doing these free readings tonight with these oracle cards
But if you'd like a more detailed reading
No, I'll give you you know
I'll put the banner up if you're interested.
There's instructions for more detailed reading
or take this in a thank you.
Okay, okay, so Montaigne, Montaigne was okay, Montaigne.
Montaigne says yes to it, okay.
Okay.
They montane this this one says thread bare self. Okay, and you can see it's like
You know, this is a little bit the edges are a little bit worn away
But sometimes when we feel a little bit worn out we going to rest right and so it says there may be depletion
worn thin frayed vitality a disconnect
stress your capacity
As the negatives but then also in the positive side, you're going to be maintaining the form need
There's a need for restoration and inner nourishment. Okay, so it says when the inner fabric wears thin
Heed the soul's whisper for rest your
Vital self calls for mending beneath the weary form
So it's like your spirit once makes you want to make sure you get rest and so that your body will be rested
Okay, because you're you're okay
No, you're fine, you're fine Cheyenne, I think I'm not sure
Okay, so I have love over coming soon one team
I'll pull another card for that a little offer coming soon. Let's see
We're good for that. Well, it looks like yeah, it looks like I look like a younger man
Maybe earth sign isn't it maybe bringing a gift or like he's like a gift her
You know, I think he might be younger though. Okay, or I don't know if you're younger or he's younger. These are usually like, you know, I
Would say in the 20s, so I don't know if that's
Okay, yeah looks like it looks like he's offering he's like oh you're 25. Okay. Yeah, perfect
Perfect he might be early in the earlier 20s
So keep an eye out for that
You'll take one after so Jamie's cowboys would like a car. Hey F. Okay. Come on. Who is that?
So Jamie this one says solitary witness
And it says
Solitary observation, detached, perceptive, unique viewpoint, clarity, potential isolation,
intuitive guidance, as the moon brings insights, okay? You're welcome. And so it says, alone on the
Then weave the insight back into your world. Okay. Hey, Birdo
You're about to lose my channel. Bye. Excuse me. What are you talking about? Oh
Yeah, so this little
This little ridiculous little monster this I think it's like it was rejected from Pokemon and so just for being too stupid
Yeah
Take it by you your channel or whatever your your threats
Okay, I'll be right back guys. I'm just gonna